# **BRYAN LUBAY**

# ENTRY-LEVEL SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

**■** bryanlubay1@gmail.com **③** bryanlubay.github.io **△** 702-606-9731 **9** Las Vegas, NV **in** bryanlubay **⑤** bryanlubay

## **SUMMARY**

I am a nine-year veteran of the United States Army and a computer science graduate from the University of Nevada Las Vegas (UNLV). For as long as I can remember, I have always loved technology - especially video games. Growing up, I was fascinated by the evolution of Super Smash Bros from SNES to N64 to current consoles. The improvements of graphics, gameplay, and fluidity fueled my passion for technology and drove me to create a 3rd-person shooter game in Unity during my junior year of college. Ultimately, this led to my creating of a Control-Find application in Android Studio during my senior year of college that represented UNLV at the 2020 Consumer Electronics Show. Whether it's creating new video games or using the Global Combat Support System to provide logistical support to my soldiers and unit solving problems, I am excited for a bright future in the computer science field!

### SKILLS

LANGUAGES: C++, Python, Java, Javascript, C#, HTML

DATABASES / SYSTEMS: PostgreSQL, Django ORM, Global Combat Support System

FRAMEWORKS / ENGINES: Django, React, Unity

METHODOLOGIES / INDUSTRY PRACTICES: Git, Github, Pair Programming, Test-Driven Development

# **PROJECTS**

#### **Battle Buddies**

A social media website for competitive video game players to socialize and set up games to play with each other.

Uses: React, Bootstrap, Django, Postgres

Github Front End: https://github.com/kiloplatoon/video\_game\_matcher\_frontend Github Back End: https://github.com/kiloplatoon/video\_game\_matcher\_backend

#### Search

A control-find tool for words on a picture that creates red squares around each instance of the word the user is looking for.

Built with Android Studio utilizing Java.

Github: https://github.com/bryanlubay/Search

#### Jim Saves The City!

A 3rd person adventure shooter video game where the user controls the main character Jim and saves the city from various monsters. Built with Unity utilizing C#.

Github: https://github.com/bryanlubay/Jim-Saves-The-City

# **EMPLOYMENT**

### **University of Nevada-Las Vegas**, *Teaching Assistant / Lab Instructor*

June 2019 - Dec. 2019

- Taught four weekly 50 minute sections of 20-30 students per section about computer science fundamentals.
- Graded and provided feedback on students' assignments and tests.

#### **United States Army**, Automated Logistical Specialist / Sergeant

Oct. 2011 - Nov. 2019

- Deployed to Kuwait as a squad leader directly responsible for 4 junior soldiers and sole logistical specialist for a company of over 100 soldiers.
- Accountable for accurate records and ordered parts on over \$20 million of equipment during one period.
- Awards: Army Commendation Medal, Army Achievement Medal, Armed Forces Reserve Medal.

### **EDUCATION**

#### **Code Platoon**

Jan. 2020 - Apr. 2020

Fullstack Software Engineering

**University of Nevada-Las Vegas**Bachelor of Science Computer Science

Jan. 2013 - Dec. 2019